<Files\\Cost_Management> - § 14 references coded  [2,10% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,28% Coverage

Tag Enablement (AWS/Azure)

Reference 2 - 0,28% Coverage

A reporting engine that works in the cloud and provides:
- Report scheduling
- Report configuration
- RBAC

* Information sources used
* Data in the report
* Calculations (i.e. cost total per group)

- Report format (header, footer)
- Group by (sub-header, information present in the

* Storage format (csv, pdf, json)
* Storage management (how long is the report stored, zip)

- Report downloading

Reference 3 - 0,28% Coverage

Reporting engine for reports

Reference 4 - 0,01% Coverage

A way to show hierarchies in clouds (like OU), in a single view that can also provide additional information about sources and their hierarchy, and the information we have about their state.

Reference 5 - 0,28% Coverage

Account based hierarchy view (aka. Money tree)

Reference 6 - 0,02% Coverage

As a cost-management user, I want to predict next month's costs so that I can make better planning decisions.

Reference 7 - 0,28% Coverage

Basic forecasting: linear regression using database data

Reference 8 - 0,03% Coverage

As a user I want a to expand my options when creating a cost model so that the cost reported better fits my needs. 

Reference 9 - 0,02% Coverage

 As a cost-management user, I want to predict next month's costs so that I can make better planning decisions.

Reference 10 - 0,28% Coverage

Basic Cost Forecasting API (Linear Regression)

Reference 11 - 0,02% Coverage

Create an installation of version of the cost management operator that works in disconnected OpenShift environments

Reference 12 - 0,03% Coverage

Create the necessary components to upload data to the cloud from a disconnected cluster, from a system that is connected to the Internet and where the information gathered from the cluster have been copied.

Reference 13 - 0,28% Coverage

Operator Enhancements - Support for air-gapped installation and workflow

Reference 14 - 0,03% Coverage

As a user I want to view the cost details of a particular AWS Organizational Unit, so that I can provide the finance department a charge or assign that cost to that organizational unit in some way.

<Files\\Jira_Performance_Testing_Tools> - § 2 references coded  [0,30% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,14% Coverage

JPT aims to help vendors gauge the performance impact of their apps, so they can test and refine it for our mutual customers. We're working on improving infrastructure provisioning, shipping enterprise-scale data sets, and providing reference traffic profiles. In its current state, you can use JPT to compare Jira's performance with and without an app.

Reference 2 - 0,16% Coverage

We want JPT to help customers test hypotheses that answer crucial questions like "how can our hardware handle an extra 12% increase in issues" or "how much would archiving 100 projects help".  To do this, JPT creates virtual users to access and use your instance, noting the response time to common user actions. JPT is also designed to operate behind your firewall, so you won't have to expose or anonymize your data.

<Files\\Lyrasis Dura Cloud> - § 1 reference coded  [0,05% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,05% Coverage

Provide a starting point for the further work of developing a large file processing capability within DuraCloud that does not rely on Amazon EMR.

<Files\\Network_Observability> - § 4 references coded  [1,09% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,04% Coverage

Create the console dynamic plugin to visualize netflow data.

Reference 2 - 0,49% Coverage

Network Observability console plugin

Reference 3 - 0,07% Coverage

Allow users to install the network observability platform that we're building to collect and visualize netflow data

Reference 4 - 0,49% Coverage

Network Observability upstream operator

<Files\\OpenShift_UX_Product_Design> - § 16 references coded  [2,43% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,38% Coverage

ACM Governance Policy Set Page

Reference 2 - 0,06% Coverage

The long term plan for the migration toolkit for virtualization (MTV) is to have a UI inside the OpenShift console. 

Reference 3 - 0,38% Coverage

Exposing Migration toolkit UI entry point in CNV navigation

Reference 4 - 0,12% Coverage

As a openshift admin who wants to install fully automated installation of openshift on Alibaba i want one-stop-shop where I can install/manage my openshift subscription  

Reference 5 - 0,04% Coverage

Using the user settings new feature (cloud sources) as a provider connection within the OCM flow.

Reference 6 - 0,38% Coverage

Integrate cloud sources in OCM

Reference 7 - 0,04% Coverage

Allow users to cut costs of running OpenShift clusters by using AWS EC2 Spot Instances. 

Reference 8 - 0,38% Coverage

Support AWS Spot instances option in machine pools UI

Reference 9 - 0,01% Coverage

The "Open search" experience on the masthead ([past vision work|#slide=id.g9a856df493_4_505]])

Reference 10 - 0,01% Coverage

Overview page with a search experience incorporated to have an "Amazon-like" experience 

Reference 11 - 0,02% Coverage

As an admin, I want to enable developers to migrate their applications and make it as easy as possible for them to take a manually deployed application and turn it into an automated deployment.

Reference 12 - 0,01% Coverage

As a developer, I want to migrate my manually deployed application to a new cluster as an automated deployment.

Reference 13 - 0,12% Coverage

As a user/developer who needs to migrate my application from a different cluster that may be 3.x, I need to easily discover the MTC operator, install it, and use it to import my apps into OpenShift.

Reference 14 - 0,04% Coverage

As a openshift admin who wants to install fully automated installation of openshift on Alibaba i want one stop shop where i can install/manage my openshift subscription  

Reference 15 - 0,38% Coverage

Enable Alibaba on https://cloud.redhat.com/openshift

Reference 16 - 0,03% Coverage

For both the Cluster creator and infrastructure owner we need a good method for managing labels. 

<Files\\Qt_Design_Studio> - § 6 references coded  [1,43% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,28% Coverage

3D content import

Reference 2 - 0,04% Coverage

*We need to support the design developer workflow. *

*This means Qt Design Studio has to support Qt for MCUs.*

Reference 3 - 0,28% Coverage

Support Qt for MCUs in Qt Design Studio

Reference 4 - 0,28% Coverage

Create a visual tool for editing the shader graph

Reference 5 - 0,28% Coverage

Navigator: 3D support

Reference 6 - 0,28% Coverage

3D editor: Basic visual editing

<Files\\Red_Hat_Developer_Website_v2> - § 3 references coded  [0,87% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,29% Coverage

Create new product page for Rust

Reference 2 - 0,29% Coverage

create new product pages for LLVM

Reference 3 - 0,29% Coverage

Create new product pages for Golang

