<Files\\Cost_Management> - § 53 references coded  [2,07% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,04% Coverage

Although a user has to specifically enable a tag in AWS, there’s little information in AWS about that tag. It’s very possible to import a tag with many (ex. 1.5M) values which negatively impacts performance in cost management. If we add tag enablement for all sources and give the user some information/education about selecting tags with a limited number of values, cost management – especially when grouping by tag – will perform better
Less is known about the limits of tags in Azure

Reference 2 - 0,03% Coverage

 * We have already done spike and PoC work toward this objective, this is just aiming for a complete solution where we process and store data using S3 and a big data tool
* Scale and process more customers

Reference 3 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I only have to go to one place for source configuration/setup. 

Reference 4 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I only have to go to one place for OCP source configuration/setup. 

Reference 5 - 0,01% Coverage

so that cost management users can see a forecast of their data.

Reference 6 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I can estimate my potential future costs.

Reference 7 - 0,08% Coverage

 This enhancement is to purge old data out of the _reporting_awsorganizationalunit_ table for the current aws organizational unit work. We can probably hook this feature into the already existing expired data celery task for the summary table. 

As the table grows there may be some likely scenarios where we may want to reduce the rows in the table to reduce the number of rows the apis have to filter out.

Reference 8 - 0,07% Coverage

Currently the json sting in the sources wizard has the minimal settings to collect basic AWS cost data, this does not include account alias names and Organisation information.

It would be great to have the ability for the user to select which data they are happy for cost management to collect then we just build the json string from that for copying.

Reference 9 - 0,11% Coverage

Cloud Watch is not enabled for koku-listener so we are not able to view OCP ingest and processing logs with Kibana

Reference 10 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I know I have improperly configured my OCP source.

Reference 11 - 0,01% Coverage

so that it is easier to diagnose issues with the operator.

Reference 12 - 0,05% Coverage

Knowing this date will give me the missing context for what data my Cost Management dashboard is showing and will give me a good sync point to verify Cost Management with other external tools.

Reference 13 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I can only see the results I want. 

Reference 14 - 0,01% Coverage

to have a better understanding of the information provided by the cloud

Reference 15 - 0,01% Coverage

in order to match my business configuration with the way the information is grouped in cost management

Reference 16 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I can define visibility based on customer hierarchies defined in AWS as OU.

Reference 17 - 0,01% Coverage

so I understand why I am seeing the numbers I am seeing

Reference 18 - 0,05% Coverage

It is hard for customers to understand how things are calculated and grouped when there is not indications to understand what has been processed and how. 
Cost management currently works at the account level but that doesn't reflect the real structure of the data we are receiving. For instance, many accounts in AWS will be part of the same source, even if those accounts have a complete different life cycle, as soon as they are grouped into a parent / children account because of financial reasons, we basically lose the detail information that is closer to the real problem that we are trying to solve.

Reference 19 - 0,09% Coverage

so that I can understand how the cost totals are being calculated.

Reference 20 - 0,09% Coverage

so that I can understand how the cost totals are being calculated.

Reference 21 - 0,04% Coverage

to help make things more readable.

Reference 22 - 0,03% Coverage

so that I can understand how the cost totals are being calculated

Reference 23 - 0,10% Coverage

so that I can understand how fresh/stale the data representing on the cost management app is.

Reference 24 - 0,02% Coverage

So that I can better model real-world data patterns

Reference 25 - 0,01% Coverage

so I can access my data. 

Reference 26 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I can make better planning decisions.

Reference 27 - 0,02% Coverage

Our customers want to understand what is going to be the expenses at the end of the month, as accurate as possible, and be able to compare it with the current data.

Reference 28 - 0,03% Coverage

Being capable of predicting costs accurately as soon as possible allows the customer to take action and increases the chances that any corrective changes has a real impact on the account governance.

Reference 29 - 0,01% Coverage

so I can know plan my budgets

Reference 30 - 0,01% Coverage

so I can know plan my budgets

Reference 31 - 0,01% Coverage

so I can know plan my budgets

Reference 32 - 0,18% Coverage

Accounts in the cloud can often be hierarchical. Depending on the business of the customer, many accounts can be organized to reflect better the requirements from the business.
AWS currently provides different organizations. In the basic one, a customer can have a master account (that accrues all data from the different accounts), and member (linked) account.
However, that is not enough for customer, so clouds offer additional ways of organizing their accounts into hierarchies.
Amazon also provides a way of organizing accounts together for management purposes (not billing). You can use organizational units (OUs) to group accounts together to administer as a single unit. This greatly simplifies the management of your accounts. For example, you can attach a policy-based control to an OU, and all accounts within the OU automatically inherit the policy.
Reflecting this organization into the account and RBAC of cost management can greatly reduce the requirements for organization inside cost management and thus make things easier for customers

Reference 33 - 0,15% Coverage

DDF dual list selector has no way to set the sorting icon. We want to use Patternfly's common sort icon while the dual list selector is using the alpha sort icon.

Reference 34 - 0,28% Coverage

DDF (data driven form library) is being used in the Settings UI to render the dual list select.
However, it is missing the text that specifies the number of items that are selected in a list.

When we are selecting items that we want to move to the other list, we do not have a way to display "<selected items> of <number of available items> selected".

This is a feature that does not exist in DDF and need to be pushed to DDF.
Settings UI is now using the latest version of DDF - so it's enough to push the change to DDF master branch (this also requires me to update DDF version in settings-ui).

Reference 35 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I can get up and running sooner. 

Reference 36 - 0,01% Coverage

so that we can offer the best initial user experience.

Reference 37 - 0,05% Coverage

so that it is available to be sent off to other sources (e.g. the DataHub), we utilize cheap long term storage, and so we can trigger events off of data entering object storage.

Reference 38 - 0,01% Coverage

so that we can distribute the processing of large manifests across many worker pods.  

Reference 39 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I have quick and convenient access to only the data I need

Reference 40 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I can understand what happened and how to fix (if applicable).

Reference 41 - 0,01% Coverage

so that we can better handle production workloads.

Reference 42 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I can limit access to cost data in cost management without duplicating effort. 

Reference 43 - 0,04% Coverage

so that my data can be ingested by cost management

Reference 44 - 0,02% Coverage

so that we create a minimal footprint.

Reference 45 - 0,01% Coverage

so that the cost reported better fits my needs.

Reference 46 - 0,03% Coverage

 * Creating the OCP source improves on-boarding as it minimizes setup
* Creating an associated Cloud source allow users to minimize locations for setup when pairing OCP with the cloud they are running it on.

Reference 47 - 0,01% Coverage

, so that I always have access to my data. 

Reference 48 - 0,06% Coverage

 * We need to tackle scaling large amounts of data as number of customer on-boarding to use cost management grows.
* We need to improve our ability to handle summarized data by partitioning it by time periods which will enable us to handle and present more data over time to users
* Keeping the raw data and daily data in the DB over time will lead to large costs $$$ to run cost management, moving this data to S3 is more affordable and is a strategy for data export + potential aligns with use in big data engines like Presto.

Reference 49 - 0,01% Coverage

I can make better planning decisions.

Reference 50 - 0,05% Coverage

 - Forecasting is a critical feature for securing a competitive advantage.
- Once we have an MVP, Forecasting is going to take time to fine-tune and shake out the more subtle bugs. So, starting this quarter aims for us to "launch" forecasting sometime around Q4/Q1.
- If we don't start now, it's unlikely we will deliver forecasting this year.

Reference 51 - 0,07% Coverage

Most of the deployment of OpenShift are done on-prem, and many of them, specifically those for big companies that are more conscious about security, are deployed in environments that are not directly connected to the Internet.
As many of those customers are those we want to use cost management so they have right now a problem to configure the operator and send data to the cloud.

As those customers are normally the biggest ones, this solution would imply an increase in our target customers.

Reference 52 - 0,02% Coverage

that I can provide the finance department a charge or assign that cost to that organizational unit in some way.

Reference 53 - 0,03% Coverage

This is a request from the RH PnT group that is trying to use Cost Management to track RH's AWS spending. This feature is a potential use case for other enterprise companies trying to get visibility into their spend.

<Files\\Jira_Performance_Testing_Tools> - § 36 references coded  [9,54% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,22% Coverage

Analysis experience and accuracy would increase 

Reference 2 - 0,01% Coverage

If an action fails due to a timeout due to poor Jira performance, the drilldown is missing. For me this is the most interesting case for the drilldown, as it is the first step towards understanding what was taking so long took so long.

Reference 3 - 0,25% Coverage

Aws infrastructure could provide running instances faster 

Reference 4 - 0,40% Coverage

`InteractionStats` is the main transport for the processed performance results/metrics. Unfortunately its API does not expose any of its fields (they are all internal). In case I want to write my own Judge or a mechanism to analyse the results it is impossible to access them. 

Reference 5 - 0,48% Coverage

The log context becomes very verbose, listing all internals of SSH VUs in every context-based logger. E.g. task timer suffers from it:  [^timing.log] 

The SSH VU details are already logged from SSH perspective and in VU logs themselves. There's no need to spread it around in log contexts.

Reference 6 - 0,29% Coverage

Right now `DataReporter` produces only raw results in form of `summary-per-cohort.csv`. To make them more consumable 

Reference 7 - 0,24% Coverage

Provisioning of some of the instance types, for example `c5d.9xlarge`, is only supported in specific AZ for some of the AWS regions, for example for `us-east`.

Reference 8 - 0,14% Coverage

Currently it is very hard to find the data for experiment and baseline for the same scenario / dataset

Reference 9 - 0,48% Coverage

When a "late" VU node fails, we still wait for the "early" nodes to finish.
This way we waste a lot of time for a result, which will not be useful anyway. It prolongs the feedback loop, especially in cases when you want to construct a repro of a early phase bug, e.g. JPERF-411

Reference 10 - 0,48% Coverage

Initially, decompression took ~19 minutes for 10 GB dataset.
I replaced `pbzip2` with `lbzip2` to utilize more threads. Decompression time decreased to 90 seconds.
Both tests were performed on an ephemeral drive.

Reference 11 - 0,48% Coverage

I've done some internal tests:

Currently, the download takes ~ 10 minutes for 10 GB dataset.
I've used `lftp` for parallel download. As a result, the download takes ~ 60 seconds and utilises up to 100% of the ephemeral drive.

Reference 12 - 0,09% Coverage

waterfall charts look unstable, looking at typical and pessimistic for 8.0 and my branch you can see the reported requests are not stable (I think there’s some bug and some requests are cut off or filtered out…)

Reference 13 - 0,48% Coverage

One of our use-cases is to create [Data Scaling Reports|https://confluence.atlassian.com/enterprise/scaling-jira-7-13-959775078.html] where we run multiple test cohorts: different datasets, deployments (DC, Server), Jira versions. Right now we use `com.atlassian.performance.tools.report.api.FullReport` that dumps `summary-per-cohort.csv` and then we manually create graphs based on the results.

That is something that could be actually done by JPT out of the box.

Reference 14 - 0,26% Coverage


I want to avoid circular dependency by extracting integration tests to a separate module. IMO it will also simplify infrastructure's `build.gradle.kts`. It wouldn't have to separate tests by class name and to introduce `testIntegration` task. Project build would be responsible for running IT.

Reference 15 - 0,37% Coverage

One of our use-cases for JPT in Jira is to provide [data scaling reports|https://confluence.atlassian.com/enterprise/scaling-jira-867028644.html]. The report runs around 40 performance tests with different configurations in a single execution. It is very costly and error prone. For example 1% of flakiness in single test run means 33% of flakiness for the whole execution. To save the time and costs 

Reference 16 - 0,48% Coverage

I need this when I want to backport some feature to earlier version.
{{gradle-release}} plugin should allow releasing from the branches whose names start with {{release/}}

Reference 17 - 0,14% Coverage

For example, if a browser dies due to JPERF-244, the VU errors spike up very quickly:

{noformat}
virtual-user-node-1 git:issue/QUICK-8-explore-hardware ❯ grep -c ERROR virtual-users.log
186482
{noformat}

The error messages and stacktraces add up to the log size, which is the dominating disk space consumer:
{noformat}
virtual-user-node-1 git:issue/QUICK-8-explore-hardware ❯ du -sh *
8.0K	cloud-init-output.log
144K	cloud-init.log
16M	diagnoses
112K	syslog
30M	test-results
4.0K	virtual-users-error.log
4.0K	virtual-users-out.log
911M	virtual-users.log
{noformat}

This makes JPT workspaces prohibitively large. They're too heavy to share, even after compression (which takes a lot of time for a 7 GB workspace).

Reference 18 - 0,01% Coverage


Reference 19 - 0,48% Coverage

StatsMeter is a part of API and InteractionStats is also a part of API, but there's no way to use it. All the fields from InteractionStats are internal. 

When I'd like to calculate percentiles, I can't use StatsMeter. As an alternative, I could use `ActionMetricsReader` and do the calculations manually, but it's also internal.

Currently, the only option is to use raw results.

Reference 20 - 0,48% Coverage

Sometimes stack creation times-out with 30 min timeout, especially when creating many stacks at once. It is possible to define stack creation timeout from `Stack` API from `aws-resources` but not possible to specify in either `StandaloneFomula` nor `DataCenterFormula` in `aws-infrastructure`.

Reference 21 - 0,48% Coverage

Sometimes stack creation times-out with 30 min timeout, especially when creating many stacks at once. It is possible to define stack creation timeout from `Stack` API from `aws-resources` but not possible to specify in either `StandaloneFomula` nor `DataCenterFormula` in `aws-infrastructure`.

Reference 22 - 0,48% Coverage

AppImpactTest is very limited, and all the advanced use cases require Kotlin knowledge. Our examples are already in Java. Migrating AppImpactTest to Java could lover entry barrier for more advanced JPT use cases.

Reference 23 - 0,48% Coverage

When tracking server side regression, it's handy to use a profiler.

Reference 24 - 0,04% Coverage

I'm exploring Jira Data Center performance across different hardware configurations.
It requires multiple benchmarks on different EC2 instance types (4) with different number of nodes (1-16). In order to improve my confidence in the results

Reference 25 - 0,02% Coverage


If I decided to explore the entire search space, it would require 4 * 16 * 2 = 128 benchmarks.
I want to save time and money 

Reference 26 - 0,01% Coverage

so it's easy to rerun the entire experiment if I'll need to change some parameters. 

Reference 27 - 0,01% Coverage


Reference 28 - 0,22% Coverage

For example, when Jira provisioning fails due to timeouts on when polling on upgrade status, there's high chance that Jira application logs will contain the answer.

Reference 29 - 0,34% Coverage

Currently some of the stacks provisioned by JPT use default Virtual Private Cloud (`StandaloneFormula`, `VirtualUsersFormula`) and others use dedicated VPC (`DataCenterFormula`). The tests that use default VPC create their own Security Groups and there is a limitation for that (SG per VPC) there is also a hard limitation for VPCs (VPCs per account).

Amazon claims that global limit per account is VPCs x SGs x SGRules <= 600,000. Even with Security Group Rules limit set to 15 (which is minimum for us) what we can do is have 200 VPCs and 200SGs per VPC. Basically because of how JPT sets up its infrastructure we (Jira team) are limited to the square root of the global limit divided by Security Group Rules limit. 

Setting an exception for default VPC and increasing Security Group only there would also solve the problem but according to Amazon it is not possible.

The only solution that is left is to drop using the default VPC and provision every single stack in dedicated VPC. 

Reference 30 - 0,23% Coverage

JPT already collects _some_ of these statistics, but it is currently not trivial to customize this data collection. It would help if we could provide a collectd configuration to specify what data to collect from the Jira nodes. Given that configuration, JPT should then provision and configure collectd on the application nodes and download the collectd results at the end of the experiment.

Reference 31 - 0,38% Coverage

Pros:
* no need for deprecation
* less constructors to maintain
* less pain for the consumers, because they no longer have to pick between different constructor signatures
* automatic support for all subsets of parameters rather than arbitrary ones
* single source of defaults
* a way distinguish different arrangements of parameters of the same type
* a sustainable way to copy objects

Reference 32 - 0,48% Coverage

Currently, there's no way to extend classes such as *IssuePage* as they are final.
This would be useful for us because we'd need to create validation methods similar to the {code:java}getSummary(){code} but looking for some specific elements in our sections.

Reference 33 - 0,08% Coverage

Many aws-infra pull requests could have been done in infrastructure, empowering the BTF feature set and reducing the total number of PRs and releases needed to ship them:

Reference 34 - 0,05% Coverage

We shouldn't rely on documentation. It's easy to skip or forget.

Reference 35 - 0,03% Coverage

when compressing the datasets, which causes it to use the default setting of 100MB memory and level 9 compression (smallest file).

{{FileArchiver().unzip()}} does not have any optional arguments.

Reference 36 - 0,03% Coverage

Note that downloading the archive itself takes much less time than decompressing it, so even if the resulting snapshot is larger the total provisioning time should be shorter

<Files\\Lyrasis Dura Cloud> - § 36 references coded  [7,74% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,20% Coverage

Currently the synctoolui assumes only one user per machine will be using the synctool.  If this assumption is incorrect

Reference 2 - 0,13% Coverage

This will help to keep the functionality of the two tools in sync."

Reference 3 - 0,24% Coverage

There have been a variety of customer questions and issues reported in using the Sync Tool which mostly boil down to the user's system not having the necessary Java version or not having Java installed at all. 

Reference 4 - 0,24% Coverage

The end goal of this integration is to allow DuraBoss to be initialized with only an account ID. All the rest of the necessary initialization information should be retrieved from the database.

Reference 5 - 0,24% Coverage

The end goal of this integration is to allow DurAdmin to be initialized with only an account ID. All the rest of the necessary initialization information should be retrieved from the database.

Reference 6 - 0,24% Coverage

The end goal of this integration is to allow DuraStore to be initialized with only an account ID. All the rest of the necessary initialization information should be retrieved from the database.

Reference 7 - 0,23% Coverage

The goal of this architecture is to replace the existing (DuraCloud 2.x) service infrastructure with a system that can more efficiently and more reliably manage actions over large content sets."

Reference 8 - 0,23% Coverage

Especially on Linux, the automatic display of the Sync Tool setup/admin screen is not reliably displayed in a browser.  Also, when is does display if there are many browser windows open it is hard to find.  

Reference 9 - 0,34% Coverage

"The current OpenStack storage provider implementation uses both the client originally provided by Rackspace (which has now been discontinued) as well as the JClouds library (which is now the client recommended by Rackspace for Java development: http://docs.rackspace.com/sdks/guide/content/java.html).  

Reference 10 - 0,28% Coverage

Currently, when walking through the initial setup wizard of the SyncTool UI, if you select a sync directory or file accidentally, there is no way to remove it except to cancel and start the wizard over

Reference 11 - 0,05% Coverage

"After requests from several trial and customer users, 

Reference 12 - 0,14% Coverage

Currently, the top level directory is ignored and not persisted in the naming of the content items that are uploaded via the sync tool. 

Reference 13 - 0,09% Coverage

When content is stored in Glacier, attempts to download, view, copy, or edit the properties of that content will result in an error (http status 409). 

Reference 14 - 0,07% Coverage

This would keep users from having to manually find the storage URL for a content item and then find a way to share it. 

Reference 15 - 0,23% Coverage

Three users within the past month have had the misunderstanding that selecting the checkbox next to a space name would then allow them to view their content. Each time I had to field either a support email or call and explain that they should *not* select the checkbox next to the space name to view the content, add content, edit content, etc. but that they should only click on the name to select/highlight the space to view the content.  

Reference 16 - 0,16% Coverage

. The failover directive, which is currently in use, allows connections to be re-established, but there is the potential for messages which were sent during the time when the connection was down to be missed.  

Reference 17 - 0,14% Coverage

The reason this is an issue, is because the full command used to run the sync tool remains available in the process list of the machine on which the sync tool is running.  

Reference 18 - 0,13% Coverage

In DurAdmin, each space name has to its left a checkbox. Users expect that selecting the check box will perform the same action as selecting the space name text. Instead, selecting the checkbox (of one space or more) brings up a multi-select display.  A user from UCAR/NCAR was recently caught by this issue, and could not understand why the listing of content items was not showing up until they contacted Carissa for assistance

Reference 19 - 0,13% Coverage

Three users within the past month have had the misunderstanding that selecting the checkbox next to a space name would then allow them to view their content. Each time I had to field either a support email or call and explain that they should *not* select the checkbox next to the space name to view the content, add content, edit content, etc. but that they should only click on the name to select/highlight the space to view the content

Reference 20 - 0,34% Coverage

"As the synchronization of content between storage providers becomes automated (DURACLOUD-642), it becomes unnecessary for users to edit content in their secondary provider. In order to maintain an assurance that content remains consistent between providers, the ability for users to make changes at their secondary storage provider should be removed. They would still be able to view and download all content, but no add/update/delete operations would be allowed.  

Reference 21 - 0,11% Coverage

This would be especially useful if one needed to extract a large number of small files. You could select items either based on a search query or a list of contentIds.  I was envisioning it would work both at the durastore as well as duradmin levels.  You would issue a request for an archive and immediately receive a handle.  

Reference 22 - 0,38% Coverage

There are a few reasons for this transition:  1. Oracle has announced that Java 6 will hit end-of-life in Nov 2012 (http://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/eol-135779.html) 2. Java 7 has been available for over a year, and is becoming more prevalent 3. Java 7 has new capabilities. One specific need is the capability (in NIO) to read/write file creation, modification, and access timestamps 4. We need to support customer use of Java 7 with our client-side tools (e.g. sync tool)"

Reference 23 - 0,06% Coverage

Based on feedback from the State of North Carolina

Reference 24 - 0,29% Coverage

"The Sync Tool currently generates three logs: complete.log, duracloud.log, and synctool.log. It was noted by the SaaS4 customer that these logs together took up an unnecessarily large amount of hard drive space. They noted that over 10 days, after pushing 500 Gb of data, the logs totaled around 300 Gb. This is clearly too much space consumed by logs.  

Reference 25 - 0,12% Coverage

 This is particularly important to allow the SyncTool to continue to run normally across DuraCloud instance upgrades.   

Reference 26 - 0,35% Coverage

"As the synchronization of content between storage providers becomes automated (DURACLOUD-642), it becomes unnecessary for users to edit content in their secondary provider. In order to maintain an assurance that content remains consistent between providers, the ability for users to make changes at their secondary storage provider should be removed. They would still be able to view and download all content, but no add/update/delete operations would be allowed.  

Reference 27 - 0,44% Coverage

"The current method of replacing /x-duracloud-admin/logo is not so user friendly."

Reference 28 - 0,31% Coverage

"When an admin is logged in and looking at the space detail, the pie charts will display below the fold.  In order to see them, the user scrolls down.   However when the user clicks on a line chart data point, the pie graphs will be updated, but the user will not notice because they are not visible.   

Reference 29 - 0,44% Coverage

"Pie charts not visible on history line graph data point click"

Reference 30 - 0,16% Coverage

"Now that the Executor is in the business of running services on behalf of users, we should ensure that users aren't able to interfere with those activities

Reference 31 - 0,13% Coverage

This would allow for providing the ""green bar"" of bit-integrity health for each item.

Reference 32 - 0,25% Coverage

Currently it is not exactly clear that the left-hand y-axis represents cumulative file size, and that the right-hand y-axis represents cumulative file counts."

Reference 33 - 0,21% Coverage

"As more and more important information for the management of DuraCloud is pushed into the x-duracloud-admin and x-service-out spaces, it becomes increasingly important that the files in those spaces not be removed or changed. 

Reference 34 - 0,20% Coverage

"From a preservation perspective, it is often a concern that files stored in DuraCloud can be accidentally overwritten. This is especially an issue when tools (such as the sync tool) are used to monitor local files for changes an copy them to DuraCloud, since a file that is accidentally changed would then overwrite the good file in the backup DuraCloud system.  

Reference 35 - 0,23% Coverage

not create memory leaks The memory leak can be seen by re-deploying the DuraCloud webapps and noticing that there are warnings in catalina.out and that the old processes are not destroyed. 

Reference 36 - 0,21% Coverage

It has been a common question from trainees regarding whether a DuraCloud content item has a unique persistent URL (regardless of which storage provider(s) it is stored in). In particular, users who wish to embed content into their own applications want a URL that will not change regardless of where they have chosen to store the item. 

<Files\\Network_Observability> - § 10 references coded  [1,45% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,07% Coverage

It would allow to speed up flow reception which can take up to 10 minutes otherwise.

Reference 2 - 0,16% Coverage

This will make it easier to read the table.

Reference 3 - 0,02% Coverage

for performance and security reasons.

Reference 4 - 0,13% Coverage

Currently only dev-mode is supported while fetching loki, "dev mode" meaning having the plugin deployed on host, port-forwarding Loki to localhost:3100, etc.

Reference 5 - 0,24% Coverage

Some best practices are being discussed by email and there's a related pending PR here: https://github.com/operator-framework/operator-sdk/pull/5353

We should make sure we comply to these best practices.

Reference 6 - 0,11% Coverage

e current process involves some (de)serialization that surely can be avoided. Cf

Reference 7 - 0,15% Coverage

Currently our two plugins use json to receive and produce data. Goflow2 supports protobuf, which we should use for better performances.

Reference 8 - 0,29% Coverage

The console requires to know the network type capabilities to show/hide some Network Policy form fields.

As a result of https://issues.redhat.com/browse/NETOBSERV-27, this logic is implemented as a features document inside the console code. The console fetches the network type from the network operator and checks the supported features towards this document.

However, this limits the feature to admin users, as other logged-in users do not have permissions to fetch the network type.

Reference 9 - 0,18% Coverage

The netflow plugin for fluentd doesn't support IPFIX, so we have to use a different plugin to support IPFIX.

Reference 10 - 0,10% Coverage

Note, there's already an existing plugin [1] (downstream version used for cluster-logging: [2]), but what we need slightly differs: the existing plugin has the pod already identified through filename when the logs are processed by fluentd; whereas we need to lookup pods from source and destination IPs contained within the flow data.

Also, we're not trying to create a plugin for a generic use, so unlike this existing plugin, ours can be tailored for our needs and be rid of unnecessary options in our use case.

<Files\\OpenShift_UX_Product_Design> - § 47 references coded  [4,48% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,06% Coverage

 To make it more practical for larger deployments

Reference 2 - 0,08% Coverage

 * Subscription settings are not conducive to users making a connection between their evaluation expiring and the action of subscribing on the clusters list.
* The current edit subscriptions modal does not provide users with current cluster or subscription information to help users make informed decisions.
* Our goal is to make short term improvements to the Edit subscriptions modal that does not require any backend API changes. Focus on what can we do today to improve this experience.

Reference 3 - 0,03% Coverage

Transferring cluster ownership allows another individual to manage the cluster. Ownership can be transferred to other users in the same or different organization. [Link to documentation|https://access.redhat.com/solutions/4661621'].

Reference 4 - 0,02% Coverage

 * The current workflow is not conducive to users making a connection between their evaluation expiring and the action of subscribing. 

Reference 5 - 0,04% Coverage

* There are 1981 unclassified clusters. Having clusters in an unclassified state means that Red Hat does not understand what Custom Global Customer Name (GCN) the cluster is associated with. This limits Red Hat’s ability to engage with the owner of the cluster in a meaningful way which decreases chances of revenue generation, retention, and customer success.

Reference 6 - 0,05% Coverage

so that other members of my team can manage my cluster without needing org-admin.

Reference 7 - 0,10% Coverage

Currently customer can create 1:1:1 (Policy:PlacementRule:PlacementBinding) relationship only. In case they want to deploy all policies always together to the same location, there should be a mechanism to support this use case.

Reference 8 - 0,10% Coverage

 Currently customer can create 1:1:1 (Policy:PlacementRule:PlacementBinding) relationship when creating a policy. Customers and ACM consultants who have been listening to customers asked for this grouping mechanism and the page dedicated to grouped policies is in need.

Reference 9 - 0,03% Coverage

to improve accessibility

Reference 10 - 0,03% Coverage

Improve user's naming method for managed clusters 

Reference 11 - 0,06% Coverage

The cluster name help text presents wrong information with an old openshift URL address. 

Reference 12 - 0,03% Coverage

as they are displayed in the pane it could be misinterpreted that they are commercially supported under a full/maintenance phase. 

Reference 13 - 0,17% Coverage

EUS: OCP 4.6 includes support as an EUS. To represent the EUS we're planning on adding a version '4.6 EUS' in addition to '4.6' in the life cycle application where OCM pulls life cycle data. Review what changes needed to be made in OCM to accurately report cluster life cycle status for EUS.

Candidate: Minor point which we should address. In the releases page [1] we have a pane for each release, show the supported lifecycle phase and then the channels and versions available.

There is no commercial support for any candidate releases [2], as they are displayed in the pane it could be misinterpreted that they are commercially supported under a full/maintenance phase. If we want to list candidate versions for completeness, can we please find a way to indicate that they are not included and supported as part of the respective life cycle phase?

Reference 14 - 0,04% Coverage

The label matching UX delivers simple but powerful method of checking where the labels are being used. 

Reference 15 - 0,12% Coverage

The add-ons tab UI shows installation status, but would be useful to have the health status of add-on operator displayed.

Reference 16 - 0,10% Coverage

so that I can easily mark a cluster as having a "limited support" state, and be able to automate tasks around that state.

Reference 17 - 0,07% Coverage

so that I can understand which clusters might need my attention to remediate them.

Reference 18 - 0,08% Coverage

The cloud.redhat.com has a very important troubleshooting section. 

Reference 19 - 0,19% Coverage

 When policies are used for controlling OpenShift upgrades at managed cluster, not for checking security or compliance, they should be self-destroyed when they are complete or successful. Currently the ACM web UI doesn't have any indication.

Reference 20 - 0,03% Coverage

providing more information regarding the actual failure (if any) 

Reference 21 - 0,01% Coverage

for consistency and flexibility. 

Reference 22 - 0,28% Coverage

On the new Downloads page, we give access to a full set of OS/architecture choices.

But on Create cluster pages clusters we only offer OS choice, assuming the user wants the same architecture as the cluster will run on — e.g. if they're [installing on Power|https://cloud.redhat.com/openshift/install/power/user-provisioned], they'll also get Linux installer and {{oc}} binaries for Power, while it's likely the user wants x86 instead.

Similarly, the [pre-release page|https://cloud.redhat.com/openshift/install/pre-release] only offers x86 now, but other architectures exist on the server e.g. [https://mirror.openshift.com/pub/openshift-v4/s390x/clients/ocp-dev-preview/pre-release/].

Reference 23 - 0,03% Coverage

Allow users to cut costs of running OpenShift clusters 

Reference 24 - 0,03% Coverage

so that I know if I need to get support and that I am not using an unsupported cluster.

Reference 25 - 0,27% Coverage

Currently ACM has 3 different "cluster violations" messages:

#1 Policy is compliant
#2 Policy is non-compliant
#3 Policy status is unavailable for some clusters

Although we use #3 for disabled policies, the message is not accurate for them. 

Reference 26 - 0,06% Coverage

40 of OCP’s 52-ish Admin nav items are basically lists of Kube guts roughly organized by category. The ability to browse the guts of clusters is still important to Adi Admin (and to a lesser extent Abigail) but can be done without 40 primary nav items that make our experience intimidating for noobs and too click-ey for experts.

Reference 27 - 0,01% Coverage


Reference 28 - 0,01% Coverage

to make alignment in the future Hybrid Console easier.

Reference 29 - 0,17% Coverage

Currently we require a user to add a name to the boot source. The new flow should be:
When creating a boot source the name is auto populated with the name but the user can adjust if they don't like it.

Reference 30 - 0,06% Coverage

Currently when a user enters virtualization it is not super clear that the first thing they should do is add a boot source to a template. 

Reference 31 - 0,02% Coverage

Both of these experiences would eventually help the users connect the dots with changes happening to the system and resources they care about with events/logs/cost/etc. 

Reference 32 - 0,15% Coverage

OCM currently does not distinguish between "hub" clusters with ACM installed,  "spoke" clusters that an ACM hub manages, or unattached clusters that don't have any connection to an ACM hub yet.

As we start to encourage users to use ACM and Hybrid Console "Hub" UIs instead of single-cluster OpenShift Web Consoles "pets," 

Reference 33 - 0,02% Coverage

for better organization and management 

Reference 34 - 0,07% Coverage

 This feature would be powerful when a number of policies are in place. Currently there is no way to organize policies as they are added upon creation.

Reference 35 - 0,10% Coverage

policies so that he/she could manage them in an efficient way. This would play an important role especially when the customer handles a number of policies in the near future. 

Reference 36 - 0,11% Coverage

 The current ACM Governance data table doesn't provide a way to group "disabled" policies. It introduced an issue customers are forced to handle "disabled" policies one at a time across multiple pages.

Reference 37 - 0,06% Coverage

so that he/she doesn't have to do unnecessary management actions that would be reverted if the policies were created by Git.

Reference 38 - 0,15% Coverage

There are two ways to create policies in ACM: Git vs. UI/CLI. After creation, if a customer tries to manage policies created by Git, all the actions he/she takes in the UI would be reverted in a few seconds - the management should be happening in Git and this has to be known to customers to prevent unnecessary steps.

Reference 39 - 0,18% Coverage

"AWS infrastructure access" section relies in the Access control tab.

We've got feedback from customers that they can't understand what this tab means and how to use it.

Reference 40 - 0,16% Coverage

Editing the taints/labels only applies to *new* machines created within the MachinePool. We have placed a short-term fix for this based on PD-923, but we need to improve this once OSD-5225 is solved.

Reference 41 - 0,18% Coverage

The Admin Getting started resources card has the option of seeing console customizations which brings the user to Custom resource definitions with the Name filter “console”. The list is filtered there but it doesn't give much direction on what the user is looking at. 

Reference 42 - 0,04% Coverage

so they know the importance of the resources on the page.

Reference 43 - 0,01% Coverage

Standard way of delivering IPI installer to customer 

Reference 44 - 0,06% Coverage

Regardless of how we ultimately organize the navigation to make things easier for beginners, eventually users will level up to knowing exactly what they’re looking for and want a faster way to get to those pages. 

Reference 45 - 0,04% Coverage

Editing the taints/labels only applies to *new* machines created within the MachinePool. 

Reference 46 - 0,38% Coverage

It is needed for BIY case if you have specific requirements about how the VM should look like

Reference 47 - 0,38% Coverage

instance types need to be usable for discovery

<Files\\Qt_Design_Studio> - § 19 references coded  [1,68% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,09% Coverage

Random order causes lot of scanning of needed properties. 
It is unclear which properties belong together.
UI is cluttered without better organizing of things

Reference 2 - 0,06% Coverage

to prevent getting lost in the viewport

Reference 3 - 0,28% Coverage

User should be able to see range etc of a light. Different light types require different indications.

Reference 4 - 0,16% Coverage

to avoid solid color graphics to disappear in viewport

Reference 5 - 0,08% Coverage

to be able to select cameras and lights 

Reference 6 - 0,10% Coverage

This means that the result is closer to the appearance on embedded Linux devices.

Reference 7 - 0,05% Coverage

, e.g. to preserve the look perfectly

Reference 8 - 0,19% Coverage

Since the edit view lives in the qml2puppet process we have to synchronize the selection
between the Qt Creator process and the qml2puppet process.

Reference 9 - 0,04% Coverage

To have proper migration path from 3DS to DS

Reference 10 - 0,01% Coverage

In discussions with customers it was brought up 

Reference 11 - 0,03% Coverage

- At the moment it is a lot of work to name all the layers and then manually enter all the qml id's - most people seem to want them to be the same in the end. 

Reference 12 - 0,04% Coverage

Some projects follow a specific naming convention where every file must be prefixed with the project id. We could have 1 field for this and save the users a lot of time copy / pasting.

Reference 13 - 0,11% Coverage

3D scene editing requires camera that is separate from the "camera in the scene". 

Reference 14 - 0,05% Coverage

Some customers would like to replace the Text items with custom ones.

Reference 15 - 0,05% Coverage

At this point in time we do not really differentiate between QQuick3DObject 
and QQuickItem. 

Reference 16 - 0,04% Coverage

At the moment QQuick3DObjects 'pretend' to be QQuickItems which is a hack.

Reference 17 - 0,03% Coverage

 * To enable optimizing asset import

Reference 18 - 0,06% Coverage

so that it is possible to accurately set a keyframe's time.

Reference 19 - 0,22% Coverage

All Custom QML components are in flat organisation. In 3D you quickly get a mess, maybe create directory for each imported model or scene where generated QML, image assets and meshes are stored?

<Files\\Red_Hat_Developer_Website_v2> - § 20 references coded  [1,47% Coverage]

Reference 1 - 0,06% Coverage

There is a difference between how searches in the main RHD site return results for site searches and how the blog does. 

Reference 2 - 0,02% Coverage

to improve page speed. 

Reference 3 - 0,03% Coverage

In order to quickly allow outage messaging to be placed on the page in the most performant way 

Reference 4 - 0,04% Coverage

So that the pervasive red "DOWNLOAD" button can link to the correct download for the user's platform, we need some kind of javascript based OS detection. Today the button just links to the FIRST available download on the download page [4], [5], regardless of OS.

Reference 5 - 0,04% Coverage

Currently in Drupal it appears it is only possible to place custom text on the product download page after the ALL DOWNLOADS section where it is easily missed.   

Reference 6 - 0,12% Coverage

As mentioned in this document ( https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Y9fxGjhuwf1v9KAg-1Jb_euFeSMQjgFsENio6Tl1woU/edit?ts=59931d86 ) our current page structure uses the H1 tag for the logo, and the rest of the page structure is not properly using the hierarchy outlined here: https://www.w3.org/TR/2014/REC-html5-20141028/sections.html#headings-and-sections

Reference 7 - 0,29% Coverage

Following discussions with Jairus on SEO, we learned that there should be only one <h1> heading in the HTML on any given page. The archive pages – categories, author page, tag pages and front page, all have multiple <h1> enclosed post titles/links. On the front page, the first post should be the only <h1> (unless a permanent title is added later). On the category, tag and author page, all post titles should be <h2>, since the pages all already have one <h1> heading.

Reference 8 - 0,03% Coverage

to ensure that we have data and metrics in place in the code to support OneBox

Reference 9 - 0,20% Coverage

for DTM Download Tracking

Reference 10 - 0,02% Coverage

so that we can support cross-domain paths with OSIO. 

Reference 11 - 0,01% Coverage

to emphasize recommended content.

Reference 12 - 0,03% Coverage

The tool should provide details of performance improvements recommended.

Reference 13 - 0,08% Coverage

In order to reduce manual work around the RHD Weekly Dashboard 

Reference 14 - 0,15% Coverage

Not only will this reduce our time spent on a repetitive activity it will also decrease the risk of manual errors.

Reference 15 - 0,20% Coverage

A number of items have been brought up over the past few months about the usability or stability of Drupal. 

Reference 16 - 0,06% Coverage

PageSpeed score on the blog is greatly impacted by image sizes and script minimization.

Reference 17 - 0,01% Coverage

so that I can provide feedback to the author and ask questions or have a discussion

Reference 18 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I can quickly access the product info or download.

Reference 19 - 0,02% Coverage

so that I can quickly find the item I'm looking for. 

Reference 20 - 0,06% Coverage

Currently /downloads makes many REST API calls. It looks to be one per download link on the page. Also, the response to these requests returns multiple versions for the product, which is unnecessary.

